Today is photoshoot day for an event and the fox is here!
Hey again!
And she's already dressed and I'm not.
Because I'm lazy.
No, I have to get dressed now.
And then we're starting and take pictures together.
It's gonna be fun!
What are you doing?
Trying to pose.
Trying to be a model.
So now I just need to do my hair and change my shoes.
As we dwell inside the same stones
that we've made
Where nothing but earthly
pleasure seems to matter
The only light we see
is from the screens
No will to feel
or explore the forgotten
dimensions
But someday we can share
The glimpse of eternity
As the worlds are still
For a moment
But I guess we will be making history
When we all join hands
Just to watch the sky
For a moment
Our selfish lives have made us all go blind
But one day we'll awake by a bright light on the horizon
In one second every eye will see the same
And this blinding light will draw our attention
And someday we'll catch a glimpse of eternity
As the world stands still for a moment
But I guess we will be making history
When we all join hands
Just to watch the sky
For a moment
Cheers!
Bye!
We'll stand still for a moment
Then I guess we will be making history
When we all join hands